Account Manager: Hi Jordan, thanks for taking the time. How has the rollout been going for your team?
Jordan Park: Mostly good. We're seeing strong adoption in marketing and sales but engineering is stuck. They have specific integration needs we haven't covered yet.
Account Manager: That's good context. What's the engineering team's biggest blocker right now?
Jordan Park: They need the GitHub integration to work with our self-hosted instance. The cloud version works but we can't use it for compliance reasons.
Account Manager: Understood. I'll loop in our integrations team and schedule a technical call by next Tuesday. We've done self-hosted GitHub before so it should be doable.
Jordan Park: That would be great. Also, can you send me the pricing for adding another 20 seats? We want to expand to data engineering next quarter.
Account Manager: Yes, I'll send the pricing tomorrow morning. Will it be the same volume tier or a different one?
Jordan Park: Different - we'd cross into the 100-seat tier with this expansion.
Account Manager: Got it. I'll include both annual and monthly options. Anything else on your mind?
Jordan Park: One question - are we still getting custom training for the engineering team as part of the contract?
Account Manager: Yes, that's included. Once we figure out the GitHub piece I'll schedule the training session.
Jordan Park: Perfect. Thanks for everything.